eyefetch.com 2016-05-03

# 

We are committed to protecting your personal information and your privacy is very important to us. We have implemented this policy to inform you of the information we collect from you and how we use that information. By visiting Eyefetch you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy and to our Terms of Use.

Eyefetch collects personally identifiable information ("PII") about you that you specifically and voluntarily provide. PII includes information that can identify you as a specific individual, such as your name or e-mail address. Although you are required to register as a member of Eyefetch in order to use selected features on the site and participate in contests, many areas of Eyefetch can be accessed without providing any PII.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We may occasionally revise this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our services and from customer feedback. When any changes are made to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the “last updated” date at the bottom of this statement. If there are material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by prominently posting a notice on our site or by directly sending you a notification to the email address you have registered on our site. We recommend you regularly review this Privacy Policy for any updates or changes.

**What Information Do We Collect?**

You may browse the site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Once you register on the site you are no longer anonymous to us. When you place an order, we ask you to provide personal information such as your name, mailing address, billing address, telephone number, email address, credit card number and its expiration date. When you sell artwork on our Site we may also ask for PayPal, checking or bank account information to allow us to transfer your earnings to you. Finally, we also maintain a history of the products you have ordered and sales you have made. All of the information gained through this process may be used by Paradigm Shift, Inc., as well as providers of related services, in order to process your transaction.

We may also collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions taken in connection with the Site or services. We also collect information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times, and referring Web site addresses.

When you receive newsletters or promotional emails from us, we may use web beacons, customized links or similar technologies to determine whether the email has been opened and which links you click on in order to provide more focused email communications or other information.

**Email Communications**

We are very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission. We may send out e-mails with Site-related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions. You may also receive notification e-mails, which inform you of actions (e.g. sales made) that have been performed on the site. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, please visit the Email Preferences section of your User Profile and/or follow the instructions contained in the unwanted e-mail message. However, please note that in all cases you will continue to receive all system e-mails (e.g. those regarding forgotten user passwords) and legal notices (e.g. updates to our policies) from us.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Generally, Eyefetch does not share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies without your consent except to provide products or services you've requested and in the following circumstances: 

  * Eyefetch may be required to disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas, warrants, court orders or legal process or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  * It may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities, including without limitation, fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Eyefetch Terms of Use, or as otherwise permitted or required by law. We will transfer information about you if eyefetch is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Eyefetch will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the Web Site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. Eyefetch may share aggregated demographic information with business partners.
  * Eyefetch Personnel: Paradigm Shift, Inc. employees and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to user information if necessary in the normal course of Paradigm Shift, Inc. business.
  * Eyefetch displays targeted advertisements based on personal information that is exhibited in people's profiles. When you register with us, your personal information and other data will be stored and processed in the United States and this information may be subject to the laws of these jurisidictions.
  * When you post a message, your Eyefetch username that you are posting under is visible to other users.
  * If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

**IP Addresses**

IP Addresses are automatically reported by your browser each time you view a web page or consume a web service.

IP addresses may be used for various purposes, including:

  * To diagnose or service technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP.
  * To tailor advertising based on geographic area or other information derived from your IP address. Aggregate information derived from IP addresses may also be reported to advertisers.
  * To estimate the total number of users visiting Eyefetch from specific geographical regions.
  * To make sure that people are not voting for themselves or friends during contests or promotions.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive.

You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set.  
If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use Eyefetch products or services that require you to "sign in," and you may not be able to take full advantage of the Eyefetch service.  
Eyefetch uses its own cookies for a number of purposes, including to: 

  * Access your information when you "sign in";
  * Keep track of preferences you specify while you are using Eyefetch services;
  * Personalize the Content presented to you throughout the Website;
  * Display the most appropriate advertising banners, based on your interests and activity on Eyefetch;
  * Estimate and report our total audience size and traffic;
  * Conduct research to improve Eyefetch's content and services;

Eyefetch lets other companies (such as Google), that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other entities' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other entities do not have access to Eyefetch cookies.

**Notice to California Residents**

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by Paradigm Shift, Inc. and its related companies to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. With respect to these entities, this privacy policy applies only to their activities within the State of California. To make such a request, please send an email to help@eyefetch.com.

**Notice of Privacy Rights to International Users**

We collect, process, store, disclose and dispose of Personal Information that you submit to the Service or the Website in accordance with applicable United States law. Please note that the Personal Information you submit to the Service or the Website will be transferred to the United States to be processed by us in order to provide the Service to you or for such other purposes as set forth in this Privacy Policy. By choosing to voluntarily submit Personal Information to the Service or the Website, you are consenting to the transfer of such Personal Information to the United States. Please be aware that United States law may offer different levels of protection for Personal Information than may be available in your country.

**Questions?**

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Statement, the practices of Paradigm Shift, Inc., Eyefetch, or your dealings on our Websites, please contact us at help@eyefetch.com.

**Last updated on September 26, 2013**
